CHELSEA OKTAVIANY

087788636865 | chelseaoktaviany97@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/chelseaoktaviany

PROFILE SUMMARY

At least 1 year of experience in MERN stack development. Have been working mostly with MERN stack development using MongoDB, ExpressJS, React, and NodeJS for less than 1 year of experience through work projects. Skilled in team collaboration, analytical, and communication. Looking for jobs that provide opportunities for further development.

EXPERIENCE

COVID-19 Response Acceleration Task Force, Jakarta

Back-End Developer Intern (June, 2020 - September, 2020)

- Experienced as Back End Developer in building task-force website with HTML, CSS and PHP
- Knowledge on database relationship between customer, COVID history, and location
- Experienced in Data Entry and Engineering with MySQL

PT. Media Andalan Nusa

Full Stack Developer Intern (November, 2022 - February, 2023)

- Experienced in redesigning pages using Divi Builder
- Experienced as MERN Stack Developer in building website and mobile applications with MERN Stack
- Learning how to make a mobile application using Flutter, React Native, NodeJS, and RESTful API

PT. Media Andalan Nusa

Back-End Developer Intern (February, 2023 - December 2023)

- Experienced in REST API Documentation and Testing for website and mobile applications using Postman API
- Experienced in developing backend for website and mobile applications using NodeJS, ExpressJS and MongoDB
- Learning about integrating payment gateway
- Experienced in non-relational databases using MongoDB

EDUCATION

Cahaya Sakti Vocational High School (July 2014 - May 2017)

Vocational High School, Multimedia

Kalbis Institute (September 2017 - December 2021)

Bachelor of Computer Science, Informatics

GPA: 3.71 / 4.00

• Awards: Doodle Art - 3rd Place in Waffle 2017 Event Kalbis Institute

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Technical Skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, MongoDB, ExpressJS, ReactJS, React Native, and NodeJS
- Soft Skills: Debugging, Problem-Solving, Analytical, Teamwork, Communication skills
- Tools: Git, Github/Gitlab, Heroku, Visual Studio Code (IDE tool)
- Languages: Indonesian (Native), and English (Passive)
- Certifications: "HTML Essential Training", "Taxi App in React Native", and "Node.js, Express, MongoDB & More: The Complete Bootcamp 2023"